我叫罗曼
My name is Roman.
十年前  我们的飞船迫降在地球上
Ten years ago, our ship crash-landed
我们是来寻求庇护的
We came here seeking refuge,
可是人类却认为这是一场侵略
but the humans thought that it was an invasion.
那天晚上有一个人类女孩救了我
That night I met a human girl who tried to protect me.
我从没想过能再见她一面
A girl I never thought I'd see again.
我们幸存的种族奥特里安人
The surviving members of my race, the Atrians,
被聚拢隔离在一个军事防区
were rounded up and isolated inside a militarized sector.
现在是2024年
Now, it's 2024.
我们中的七个人被选中
Seven of us have been chosen to attend high school
加入政府的融合项目  去高中就读
as a part of a government integration program.
但是人类和奥特里安人仍旧互不信任
But the humans and Atrians continue to distrust each other
而我奋力保护我的族人
while I fight to protect my people
和那个救我一命的人类女孩
and the human girl who saved my life
不惜一切代价
at any cost.
《星恋》前情提要
Previously on Star-Crossed...
罗曼  这真的只是个意外
Roman, it was an accident!
-我真的很抱歉  -为什么
- I am so sorry! - Why?
是因为我爸死了  还是因为你爸开了枪
Because my father's dead or because your father shot him?
我在朱莉娅的病房里发现了这个
I found this in Julia's hospital room.
你救了她
You saved her life.
什么都没发生
It didn't happen.
-你的手臂...  -抱歉
- Hey, what happened to your... - I'm sorry.
怎么了
Arm?
他们想要为我父亲的死报仇
They want revenge for my father's death.
目标就是你们一家
They've targeted your family.
我们只和同类交往
We keep with our own kind.
我们中总有人在监视
One of us is always watching.
这问题不仅关乎我们两人
This is bigger than the two of us now.
我们不在一起会比较安全
It's safer if we're apart.
我一直在找你
I've been looking for you.
泰瑞  我没兴致
Teri, I'm not in the mood.
给我一分钟
Give me a minute.
你会有的
You will be.
根据人人影视字幕调整
感谢YYeTs.com
翻译：冰蓝   柒落安   喃喃   非燕
■
时间轴：浓子   Sage     校对：非燕   冰蓝
后期：冰河   监制：非燕   冰冰
■
星恋
第一季 第三集
昨晚没睡好啊
Rough night?
别干扰我的大脑
Stay out of my head.
你以前会求我用摄魂草
You used to beg me to use kyter leaves
让你做那些梦
and give you those dreams.
那是很久以前的事了
That was a long time ago.
我会在你的枕头下塞一片叶子
I'd slip a leaf under your pillow
在你耳边低语我们以前做的下流事
and whisper in your ear all the dirty things we used to do.
泰瑞  我们以前有很多种关系
Teri, we used to be a lot of things.
但如果你想继续做朋友  就必须停止这样
But if you want us to stay friends, this has to stop.
难以置信
I can't believe it.
我来了
I'm here.
我终于上高中了
I'm finally in high school.
我想让你的第一天很特别
I wanted your first day to be special.
眼花缭乱的储物柜  跳舞的熊在游行
Bedazzled locker, dancing bears on parade.
但是登陆日快到了
But with Arrival Day coming,
我觉得那样不大礼貌
I thought it might be in bad taste.
狂欢节后
After the carnival,
他都不愿意看我
he won't even look at me.
你做了什么
What did you do?
我没想到什么事
Nothing I can think of.
你才来学校一周
You've been in school a week,
就已经有感情问题了吗
and you already have boy problems?
高中太棒了
High school is phenomenal.
还有两天就到登陆日十周年纪念日了
The tenth anniversary of Arrival Day is in two days.
降临的奥特里安人
Families of the fallen,
以及人类学生和参与融合计划的
as well as human and Atrian students who are part of
奥特里安人学生
this integration program,
都被邀请参加纪念活动
are all invited to attend the commemoration,
那将在奥特里安人的飞船基地举行
which will be held at the base of the Atrian ship.
太棒了  自从飞船坠毁
Awesome. Like, no one's been allowed
就没人可以靠近
near the ship since it crashed.
我曾经在那艘飞船上
I've been on that ship.
你没错过什么精彩的
You're not missing anything.
世界都会关注我们
The eyes of the world will be on us.
人们想看看这种文化交流是如何进展的
People want to see how this exchange of cultures is progressing.
到目前为止  奥特里安七人组
So far, the Atrian Seven
上了人类学校  参加了人类活动
have attended human school and human events.
下一步就是将人类引入
The next step is to introduce humans
奥特里安人社会
into Atrian society.
为达到目的  这间教室的人类学生将于明天
To that end, the human students in this room have been selected
在隔离区度过一天
to spend a day in the Sector tomorrow.
隔离区以前从来没有过人类客人
We've never had human guests in the Sector before.
我们之前还以为鼠患就很严重了
We thought the rat infestation was bad.
这是人类学生头一回
It's the first time human students
进入隔离区
will have access to the Sector.
你们将名垂史册
You'll be making history.
加西亚女士
Uh, Ms. Garcia?
关于明天的隔离区访问  我有个主意
I had an idea about the Sector visit tomorrow.
什么
Yes?
我们都听过我们这边讲述的登陆日
We've all heard Arrival Day stories from our side--
人类这边
the humans--
但我们没听过奥特里安人的说法
but we haven't heard what it was like from the Atrians.
继续吧
Go on.
我觉得我们可以利用明天的隔离区拜访
I thought we could use our Sector visit tomorrow
来问问奥特里安人在登陆日的故事
to ask the Atrians for their Arrival Day stories.
埃默里不该去隔离区
Emery shouldn't come to the Sector.
许多奥特里安人依然对
There are a lot of Atrians that are still angry
我爸被枪杀的事很愤怒  开枪的是...
about my father getting shot by...
只是
It's just...
她可能有危险
Sh-she could be at risk.
我们已经镇压了恐怖分子
Well, we've dealt with the terrorists.
而且现场保安充裕
And there's ample security.
除非你知道具体的威胁
So unless you know of a specific threat?
那我觉得没什么好担心的
Well, then I see no reason for concern.
埃默里的计划会展示
Emery's project would show
我们两方都盼望着眼未来
that both sides are eager to move on.
恭喜  怀特希尔女士
Congratulations, Ms. Whitehill.
任务归你了
The assignment is yours.
真漂亮  亲爱的
Looking real pretty, sweetheart.
你真是麻木不仁
That's really insensitive!
即使你是个肌肉发达的外星人
Even for a 'roided-up alien.
这些丝带是为了纪念
These ribbons are a remembrance of those
那些在登陆日失去生命的人
who lost their lives on Arrival day.
那天  你的种族基本上毁了我们小镇
The day your kind literally crashed our town.
我知道  我当时在场
Yeah, I know. I was there.
你知道格雷森的哥哥被奥特里安人杀了吗
Did you know Grayson's brother was killed by an Atrian?
你失去了哥哥
You lost a brother?
是的  他是国民警卫队的
Yeah, he was in the National Guard.
我的种族死了一半的人
I lost half of my tribe.
在坠毁事故中活下来的人
Those who survived the crash
被王八蛋警卫开枪打死了
were gunned down by your bitch guards.
但你没看见我
But you don't see me
用根丝带把自己包起来
wrapping myself in ribbon
像包生日礼物那样  对吧
like a birthday present, now do you?
很遗憾你失去了同类
I'm sorry for your loss.
但我哥哥不是王八蛋
But my brother wasn't a bitch.
继续往前走
Let's keep it moving.
好吧
Right. Yeah.
朱莉娅
Julia.
-那是什么  -相机
- What is that? - A camera.
格洛丽亚的
From Gloria.
我自告奋勇在隔离区时
I volunteered to interview the Atrians
去采访奥特里安人
while we're in the Sector.
太棒了
That's amazing.
以前不许带相机进隔离区的
Cameras are never allowed in the Sector.
她让你在隔离区进行拍摄吗
And she's letting you shoot there?
你都不会用开罐器
You can barely work a can opener.
你到底为什么要这样做
Why are you really doing this?
你去那里安全吗
Is it even safe for you to be there?
格洛丽亚说一直会有警卫照看我们  而且
Gloria said we're gonna have guards watching us the whole time, and...
这个项目是罗曼父亲的梦想
this program was Roman's father's dream.
我想我帮忙的话  就能...
And by helping, I think that...
好吧  虽然我半辈子都待在医院里
Okay, I've been in a hospital half my life
但连我都知道打动男生的方法不是
and even I know the way to a boy's heart is not
通过完成他死去父亲热心的项目
through his dead father's passion project.
你到底要不要帮我
Are you gonna help me or not?
你有空
You have a free period,
而且你可以教我摄像
and you could help with the camera.
其实我得去见学校辅导员
Actually, I have to go see the school counselor.
晚一点吧
But maybe later?
如果你要找摄影师
You know, if you're looking for a cameraman,
我认识一个超棒的独立电影导演
I actually know this great indie film director
他觉得拍摄隔离区会棒极了
who just thinks that shooting the Sector would be amazing.
是吗
You do?
报酬给花生就好
And he'll work for peanuts.
我得到这份工作了吗
So do I got the job?
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
现在不方便
This isn't a good time.
你什么态度
What's with the 'tude?
当我和埃默里溜进隔离区找柏草时
You were plenty friendly when Emery and I
你友好多了
snuck into the Sector for cyper.
-我真记不起来了  -那我就提醒你
- I really don't remember. - Then I'll remind you.
我在找我癌症的神奇解药
I was looking for a miracle cure for my cancer,
和你一样
as you do.
但你说柏草只是烹饪草药
But you said cyper was just a cooking herb.
真奇怪
Funny thing...
第二天我就完全痊愈了
the next day I was completely cured.
之前我还昏迷不醒  有白血病的症状
One minute I was all comatose and leukemia-y.
接下来  我就坐了起来  吃着烤辣味干酪玉米片
The next, I was sitting up and eating nachos.
你康复了我很高兴
I'm glad you're better.
但那和我有什么关系
But what does this have to do with me?
我觉得和你关系大了去了
I think it has everything to do with you.
你和柏草
You and cyper.
你确定烤辣味干酪玉米片
You sure those nachos weren't laced
没加别的料吗
with a little something extra?
好吧
Fine.
我去和医生们分享我疯狂的猜测
I'll just go and share my insane suspicions with my doctors.
我敢肯定他们会很感兴趣的
I'm sure they'll be very intrigued.
我就知道
I knew it!
你用柏草救了我的命  对吧
You saved me using cyper, didn't you?
不管你觉得发生了什么事
Whatever you think happened,
都得保密
you need to keep it to yourself.
如果柏草能治愈癌症
If cyper can cure cancer,
难道你不想让别人知道吗
Don't you want the world to know?
好吧
Okay.
你说得对  我的确救了你
You're right, I did save you.
我把柏草浸在血液里
I infused cyper into my bloodstream
然后给你输了血
and then injected my blood into you.
但是如果世人发现了这个真相
But if the world found out about this,
谁的孩子  朋友或者宠物病了
every human with a sick child, friend or pet
都会把隔离区翻个底朝天
will be tearing apart the sector,
寻找柏草和奥特里安人的血
looking for cyper and Atrian blood.
如果我的族人知道
And if my people found out
是我为了救一个善良但管不住嘴的人类
that I put them at risk to save a nice,
而将他们置于危难之中  后果真的很严重
but very chatty human being, there will be consequences.
对咱俩都没好处
Bad ones for both of us.
所以我请求你
So I'm asking you please
能保守这个秘密吗
can you keep this a secret?
可能有一点小问题
That might be a problem.
为什么
Why?
干什么
What are you doing?
从狂欢节我碰了你开始就这样了
It started when I touched you at the carnival.
而且一直在扩散
And it's been spreading ever since.
如果你想保守柏草的秘密
If you want to keep cyper a secret,
你得先解决这个
you're gonna have to fix this.
准备好迎接人类客人了吗
Are you ready for our human guests?
我们有选择吗
Do we have a choice?
你爸会不惜一切只为见证这一刻
Your father would have given anything to see this day.
我以为你会更狂热
I thought you'd be more enthusiastic.
更兴奋
Excited.
埃默里·怀特希尔会来
Emery Whitehill is coming.
记住  你承诺过
Remember, you gave me your word
保证她不被龙头帮伤害
that you would keep her safe from the Trags.
他爸枪杀了我们敬爱的首领
Her father did shoot and kill our beloved leader.
龙头帮见到她  一定想取她性命
The Trags see her, they will want her head.
但是他们不会在公开行动
But they will not act in the open.
所以别担心
So don't worry.
如果你爸看到你如此关心一个人类
Your father would be very touched to see you
一定会很感动
So concerned for a human.
他才刚刚开始教会我这么多
There's just so much he was beginning to teach me...
关于如何当一名首领
about being a leader,
关于我们的部族
about our tribe,
关于  柏草
about... cyper.
他一定认为你已经准备好了
He must have thought you were ready.
我只是想象不到要为一个人的生命负责
I just can't imagine being responsible for someone's life.
我是说  如果出了岔子怎么办
I mean, what if something went wrong?
总会有一些副作用
Oh, there are side effects:
有时疲惫  有时狂喜
there's fatigue, euphoria.
总比死亡要好
Well, that's preferable to death.
还有什么我应该知道的事情吗
Is there anything else I should know?
有一些很罕见的例子
Well, there are some rare cases
病人没有痊愈
where the patient doesn't recover,
或者他们的血管变成了蓝色
or their-their veins turn blue.
我不确定自己会相信这个
I don't know if I believe that.
我从没见过蓝色的奥特里安人
I've never seen a blue Atrian.
因为有一种解药
Well, that's because there's a cure.
伊瓦巴斯族有一种植物  叫还原根
It's called vyre. The Iwabas tribe grow it.
窍门是  你必须在蓝色固定下来之前
The trick is, you gotta get it to the patient
让病人服下去
before it becomes permanent.
人类囚禁我们  支配我们的生活
The humans imprison us, run our lives,
现在又想像逛动物园一样在隔离区散步
and now they want to walk around the sector like it's a zoo?
当心点  你听起来快变成龙头帮了
Careful. You're beginning to sound like a Trag.
至少龙头帮愿意为族人而战
At least the Trags are willing to fight for our people.
带我们逃出监狱
Get us out of this prison.
不要融合  还我地球
No race mixing! Earth for earthlings!
刚看见你在和卡斯特叔叔谈话
Saw you and uncle Castor talking.
你接受他了
Did you come around on him?
他能帮得上忙
He can be helpful.
但是爸爸从来不相信他
But dad never trusted him.
我们也不应该相信他
Neither should we.
即使是周六  红鹰也要在
The Red Hawks protest just outside the Sector gate
隔离区门外抗议吗
even on a Saturday?
仇恨永不停歇
Hate doesn't take a weekend.
可以了吗
Shall we?
你们两两分组
You've been put in groups of two.
参观期间每组都必须有一名警卫陪同
Each pair must be accompanied by a guard during your visit here.
欢迎来到隔离区
Welcome to the Sector.
你真觉得这时候适合买纪念品吗
You really think this is the best time to be buying souvenirs?
我感觉蓝色血管要爬到脖子上去了
I can feel the blue veins growing up my neck,
所以  是的
so, yeah, I do.
好消息是有一种解药  坏消息是
Okay, good news is there is a cure. Bad news,
如果不在血管
if we don't get you that cure
蔓延到脸上前到解药  它们就治不好了
before the veins reach your face, it'll be permanent.
快跟我说你有这种解药
Please tell me you have the cure.
我需要点时间
I need some time.
中午我们还在这里见面吧
Can you meet me back here at noon?
罗曼
Roman.
我能不能用格洛丽亚的摄像机
I was wondering if we could interview you
采访你和索菲娅
and Sophia for Gloria's video.
我在想能在你家里拍摄吗
I was thinking we could shoot it in your pod?
不行  你们必须待在主要区域才更安全
No, you need to stay in the main areas where it's safer.
那么你愿不愿意介绍几个
Then would you mind introducing us
不介意分享他们登陆日故事的
to some atrians who wouldn't mind
奥特里安人给我们
sharing their arrival day stories?
我觉得你应该关注下自己的幸存故事
I need you to focus on your survival story...
就这一次
For once.
如果愿意  你们可以采访我
You can interview me if you like.
我很乐意带你们参观我家
I'd love to have you visit our pod.
要过一会儿  等我妈不在的时候
Later, when my mother's not around?
-谢谢你  太好了  -是啊
- Thank you. That would be great. - Yeah.
不  是棒极了
No, awesome.
这是市集上能帮你降压的好东西  多罗草
Now, the best bang for your buck in the marketplace? Dovor.
会有一点柔顺圆滑的嗡嗡声
Gives you a nice smooth buzz,
不会太厉害  会让你感觉
but not too much. It'll make you feel like
像是被金砖砸到头一样
you got hit in the head with a gold brick.
你不能向人类出售毒品
You can't sell drugs to humans.
我们走
Let's go.
总有一天我们不会再默默忍受
One day, we're not gonna take it anymore.
总有一天我们会摧毁围墙
One day, we're gonna break down these walls,
你们会后悔的
and you'll be sorry.
听着  帮我个忙
Now listen, um, I need a favor.
我在找还原根
I'm looking for vyre.
能从你们族的种植园里拿点吗
Can you get some from your tribe's grow house?
你要它干什么
Why do you need it?
只是
Just...
你不说我就不帮你
I'm not helping unless you tell me.
好吧  我可能是在人类身上用了柏草
All right, I-I may have used cyper on a human.
我得在别人发现之前
I need the vyre to fix
解决它的副作用
the side effects before anyone finds out.
你在谁身上用了
Who'd you use it on?
这不重要
That's not important.
你向人类展示了怎么使用柏草
You showed a human how cyper is used?
很多奥特里安人都不知道怎么用呢
Most Atrians don't even have that information.
-如果龙头帮发现  -是的  我知道
- If the Trags find out... - Yeah, I know.
所以我才求你帮我
That's why I'm asking you.
你是我唯一能够信任帮我的人
You're the only person I can trust that can help me.
或许你得给我一个站在你这边的理由
Maybe I used to have a reason to be on your side,
但是既然你早上那么说  没门
but like you said this morning, it's over.
维加
Vega.
龙头帮尊敬我  让我当他们的领袖
The trags have honored me by making me their leader.
知道你为什么在这儿吗
Do you know why you're here?
知道
I do.
你怎么回答
What is your answer?
我以我眼  我手  我心
誓死效忠龙头帮
我已经期待已久了
I've waited a long time for this.
博蒙特的标记看不见了
Beaumont's marks can't be seen,
但这些印记却和你的一样深入骨髓
but they run as deep as yours.
在你成为真正的龙头帮成员之前
Before you become a full brother of the Trags,
你必须证明自己
you must prove yourself.
我们已经观察你一段时间了
We've been watching you for some time.
如今命运选择了你
And now destiny has chosen you.
十年来
For ten years,
奥特里安人被禁止进入我们的飞船
no Atrian has been allowed access to our own vessel,
但是我们听说你和奥特里安七人组
But we hear you and the Atrian seven
受邀参加在坠毁点举办的纪念活动
have been invited to the commemoration at the crash site.
明天你要闯进飞船里
Tomorrow you will break into our ship,
然后  我们来一起摧毁人类
and together, we will lay waste to the humans.
当我们被安置在隔离区
When we were put in the sector,
我爬上屋顶俯瞰整个城镇
I'd go up on the rooftop and look at the town.
我迫不及待地想亲自探索那些灯光
I couldn't wait to explore those lights for myself
结识生活在那里的人们
and meet the people living there.
在隔离区里  这样有点困难
It's a little hard to do from the sector,
但此时此刻
but in the meantime,
有两个人正在我的家里
I have two of those people in my pod.
再次谢谢你邀请我们
Thank you again for inviting us.
你是否介意我
Do you mind if I...?
请便
Go ahead.
这是什么
What is it?
不知道  罗曼一直留着它
I don't know. Roman's had it forever.
他说过是从哪得到的吗
Did he say where he got it?
太久远了  我不确定他还记不记得
It's been so long, i don't know if he even remembers.
罗曼
Roman!
我告诉过你  可你还是请他们来了
You invited them here after I told you not to?
妈妈发现了怎么办
What if mom finds out?
-不会的  -是我的错
- She won't! - This is my fault.
是我要求采访她的
I asked to interview her.
-你们的警卫呢  -他在楼下等着
- Where is your guard? - He's downstairs waiting.
那你们也应该在楼下
Then that's where you should be.
和警卫还有枪在一起
With your guard and his gun.
哥们  放轻松
Dude, you need to relax.
我跟你说话了吗
Was I talking to you?
好了  我们现在就走
It's fine. We're leaving.
这些斯瓦迈德族的植物是用来耕种的
The plants of the Swamad tribe are used for farming.
必要但是乏味
Necessary, but boring.
现在  兹瓦汉族有一种草药  柏草
Now, the Zwahan have just one herb-- cyper.
它能挽救濒死之人
It can bring someone back from the brink of death.
令人印象深刻  除非是在战场上
Sounds impressive, unless you're in a fight,
它就没用了
in which case it's useless.
事实上  奥特里安人的幸存全依赖于
The fact is, the survival of all Atrians depends on the plants
我们部族的植物和技艺
and skills of our tribe,
瓦萨克族  和我们的勇士
the Vwasak, the warriors.
带上锁喉草  它能让任何一点接触
Take sovok, it can turn any pressure point
变成死亡的宣判
into a death sentence.
头顶  颈部还有腹股沟
The top of the head, the neck, the groin.
如果你想加入龙头帮
If you want to join the Trags,
就必须向我证明你自己
you need to show me something!
我们绝不会让一个没有经验的学生
We can't have an untrained schoolboy
为我们奔走效力
running around carrying out our orders!
你是怎么去掉你的胎记的
How'd you get rid of your birthmarks?
你必须在外面生存
I mean, you had to, right, to live on the outside?
那你在外面都看到了些什么
What have you seen out there?
你去过埃尔吉大吗
Have you been to Eljida?
你问题可真多
That's a lot of questions.
但如果你真的想成为勇士
But if you truly want to be a warrior,
只需扪心自问一个问题
there's only one question you should be asking yourself.
你愿意为了自己奋斗的目标而杀人吗
Are you willing to kill for your cause?
这才像话
Now we're getting somewhere.
你怎么摆脱警卫的
How'd you get rid of the guards?
我不停地向他们介绍
I talked on and on about
我极具特色的奥特里安玩偶收藏
my specialty Atrian doll collection.
他们马上溜之大吉了
They couldn't get away fast enough.
你搞到解药了吗
So, do you have the cure?
没有  但我知道去哪里弄
No, but I do know how to get it.
我在想
Listen, I was thinking,
也许我们应该告诉埃默里我们在做什么
maybe we should tell Emery what we're doing.
不行
No.
我就知道你会这么说
I thought you might say that.
只是你表现得太混蛋了
It's just you've been kind of a jerk,
她现在真的很受伤...
and she's really hurting right now and...
她看上去没什么问题啊
Seems like she's doing just fine.
你明明很关心她
You obviously care about her.
你背叛你的族人  救了一个人类
You betrayed your people to save a human.
都是为了她
And you did it for her.
在埃默里父亲做出那件事之后
After what Emery's father did,
很多奥特里安人都巴不得她死
there's a lot of Atrians who would rather see her dead
而不是看到她和我在一起
than see her with me.
你为什么不跟她这么说
Why can't you tell her that?
狂欢节上我就试图告诉她她处于危险之中
I tried to tell her that she was in danger at the carnival.
但也没能阻止她今天到隔离区来
Didn't stop her from coming to the Sector today.
她就是那么固执
She is stubborn like that.
她和我走得越近
The closer she is to me,
就越...
the more danger...
就越危险
...the more danger she is in.
我在尽我所能改变这情况
I'm doing everything I can to change that.
但是在那之前
But until then,
如果做个混蛋是保护她的唯一方法
if being a jerk's the only way to keep her safe,
那我就必须这么做
then that's what I'm gonna have to be.
走吧
Come on.
龙头帮让德雷克入伙了
So, the Trags have enlisted Drake.
他们要那个莽汉干吗
What do they want with such a blunt instrument?
他们奥特里安七人组
He and the Atrian Seven
都已经收到去飞船
have been invited to the ship
参加纪念活动的邀请
for the commemoration.
龙头帮想让他闯进飞船里
The Trags want him to break into the vessel.
确保我们能生存下去的最好办法
Best way to ensure our survival
不是停止龙头帮和人类之间的战争
is not to stop the war between the Trags and the humans,
而是确保我们一直处于优势
but to always make sure we're on the winning side.
你一直都在监视罗曼和埃默里·怀特希尔吗
Have you kept your eye on Roman and Emery Whitehill?
他一直都和那个女孩保持距离
He's been keeping his distance.
别让他耍了你
Don't let him fool you.
他喜欢她
He likes her.
这让事情变得更复杂
Which complicates things.
你想让我把她解决掉
You want me to take care of her?
不
No.
我来对付她
Leave her to me.
拍到了不错的照片
Think we got some good stuff.
朱莉娅在哪儿
Where's Julia?
她又丢下了我
I think she ditched me again.
我赢了吗
Did I just win?
你拍的那些照片
The pictures you take.
隔离区外面的人能看到吗
Can people outside the Sector see them?
当然
Yeah.
那是我的妈妈
That's my mom.
登陆日那天她离开了我们
We lost her on Arrival Day
当时我还是个婴儿
when I was a baby.
爸爸说她现在住在埃尔吉大
My dad said she lives in Eljida now.
但总有一天我们会再次团聚的
But one day we'll all be back together.
你现在能把我录下来吗
Can you record me now?
当然可以
Sure.
妈妈  是我  莉莉
我已经长大  你可能认不出我了
我为我的奥特里安同胞道歉
I apologize for my fellow Atrians,
但这里是他们的圣地
but this place is sacred to them.
他们不喜欢擅自闯入的人
They don't look kindly on interlopers.
这是什么地方
What is this place?
这是失踪者之墙
This is the wall of the missing.
我们一住进隔离区就建起了它
This was created when we were first placed in the sector.
用来纪念那些
It's a memorial for all the family members
在登陆日失踪的家人
that were lost on Arrival Day.
那个小女孩说她的妈妈还活着
That girl said her mom's still alive.
一些奥特里安人相信
Some Atrians believe
失踪的人逃跑了
that the missing escaped
为自己建造了家园
and made a home for themselves:
叫埃尔吉大
Eljida.
埃尔吉大真的存在吗
Does Eljida really exist?
谁知道呢
Who knows?
但是它给予了他们希望
But it gives them hope.
我叫卡斯特
I'm-I'm Castor.
罗曼的叔叔
I'm Roman's uncle.
你们俩是朋友  这真有趣
I-I find it interesting that you two are friends.
有什么有趣的
What's interesting about it?
你的父亲  还有他的父亲
Well, your father, his father,
那场不幸的意外
the unfortunate accident.
我想罗曼并没把我当朋友
I don't think Roman would consider us friends.
那他把你当成什么呢
What would he consider you?
我得走了
I should go.
我的朋友们可能都在等我了
My friends are probably waiting for me.
好的
Of course.
我们这是在哪
Where are we?
伊瓦巴斯族的种植房
The grow house of the Iwabas,
一个神秘的部族
the mystic tribe.
我们要找一种长着红色细枝的植物
We're looking for a plant with red twigs.
叫还原根
It's called Vyre.
越快找到它
The faster we find it,
就能越快离开这里
the faster we can get out of here.
罗曼
Roman.
你在这里干什么
What are you doing here?
那个...
Well...
门没有关
The door was open,
我就想进来看看
and I-I just had to look.
我一直都对伊瓦巴斯族的植物很着迷
I've always been fascinated by the plants of the Iwabas.
我们的植物是所有部族中种类最多
Our plants are the most varied
也是最有意思的
and interesting of all the tribes.
比如说
This one,
这个
for example.
剥皮果
Bylek.
当它进入你的脊髓之后
When plunged into your spinal cord,
你的感觉神经和运动神经都会瘫痪
it paralyzes your sensory and motor nerves,
你的痛觉感受器会被激发
causing your pain receptors to fire.
你会感觉像是被活剥了皮一样
It will feel like you're being skinned alive.
现在
Now...
告诉我你到这里的真正目的
why don't you tell me what you're really doing here?
最后的机会了  罗曼
Last chance, Roman.
我告诉你的是事实
I told you the truth.
-才不是  -妈
- Wrong answer. - Mom?
泰瑞
Teri.
我正准备告诉你妈妈
I was just about to tell your mother
我们有约会的事
that we had a date.
就在这里
Here.
这是真的吗
Is this true?
是的
Yes.
你刚才怎么不说
Why didn't you say so before?
恕我直言
Well, with all due respect,
只因为我出现在草药房你就要拷问我
you were going to torture me for just being in the grow house.
如果我告诉你我要和你女儿见面
I didn't know what you'd do to me
不知道你还会做出什么事情
if I said I was gonna meet your daughter.
别让我再在这里抓到你
Don't let me find you here again.
没事了
It's fine.
你要当心罗曼
You should be careful with Roman.
他和他爸都对人类有反常的爱
He shares his father's same perverse love for the humans.
你在他的影响下正变得脆弱
His influence is making you weak.
说完了吗
Are you done?
罗曼让你无法接受自己的命运
Roman is keeping you from embracing your destiny.
作为这个部族的一员
As a member of this tribe.
作为龙头帮的一员
As a Trag.
作为我的女儿
As my daughter.
不久后的一天
One day soon,
你必须选择效忠于谁
you will have to choose where your loyalties lie.
是罗曼
With Roman...
还是你的家族
or with your family.
格洛丽亚的视频已经有了几个采访
We actually have a few interviews for Gloria's video.
不光是那些你被奥特里安人骂的视频
Not just footage of you getting yelled at by Atrians.
明天的纪念活动
The commemoration tomorrow...
你的家人肯定很难接受
It must be hard on your family.
你肯定很想念你的兄弟吧
I'm sure you're thinking about your brother a lot.
我觉得每个到场的人都很难接受
I think it'll be hard for everyone there.
奥特里安人到场时他们会有什么感受
How are they gonna feel when the Atrians show up?
说实话
Honestly?
很多人都会感到厌恶
I think a lot of people will hate it.
对我们的视频也是
And our video.
如果你是这么想的
Well, if you thought that,
那你为什么要主动帮我呢
then why'd you offer to help me?
你看上去需要帮助呗
You seemed like you needed it.
而且我也想吃炸泡菜了
And I wanted some fried pickles.
奥特里安人登陆十周年纪念日
-那是你的父母吗  -是的
- Your parents? - Yeah.
-你的妈妈很  -古板
- Your mom's so... - Stuffy?
势利  高冷
Snobby? Emotionally remote?
我本来想说很优雅的
I was going to say elegant.
我给格洛丽亚看了视频
I showed Gloria the video,
她很喜欢
and she loved it.
不过我们必须立马上传
But we have to upload it right now.
我来办
I'm on it.
给我留个座
Save me a seat?
好的
Yeah. Sure.
罗曼
Roman...
这是还原根
It's vyre.
我这么做只是为了让我妈不拷问你
I'm only doing this to keep my mother from torturing you.
谢谢
Thank you.
小心点
Be careful.
没人知道还原根对人类能起什么作用
No one knows how vyre works on humans.
它能治愈柏草的副作用  可...
It will cure the side-effect of cyper, but...
说不准还有什么作用
There's no telling what else it will do.
走起来
Keep it moving.
我拿到了
I have it.
还原根
The vyre.
谢天谢地
Thank god.
我要拿它做什么
What do I do with it?
吃下去
You eat it.
可是
But...
或许这风险太大了
Maybe this is too big a risk.
你都这么警告我
After all of your warnings
公开柏草的秘密的后果了  还怕冒这险
about exposing the secret of cyper?
听着  如果有人发现我是怎么被治愈的
Look, if anyone finds out how I was cured,
他们也会把我关在实验室里
they'll lock me up in a lab, too.
我在医院待的时间够长了
I've spent plenty of time in the hospital.
我不会再回去了
I won't go back to that.
再说
And besides...
你救了我的命
You saved my life.
这是我起码能做的
This is the least I can do.
先生  你得跟我走一趟
Sir, I need you to come with me.
欢迎大家[外星语]
欢迎大家
Welcome.
今天我们缅怀逝者
Today we honor those we've lost,
可我们也展望未来
but we also look to the future.
是时候了
It's time.
我把通往飞船的安全门弄失灵了
I've disabled the security gate that leads into the ship.
你应该能进出自如了
You should be able to get in and out undetected.
不行的话...
But if not...
就把他们敲死
...Knock 'em dead.
我可以告诉你们
I could tell you
我们这项融合项目的成功
about the success of our integration program,
但我要让你们亲眼看到成果
but I'll let you see the results for yourselves.
登陆日故事 10周年纪念日
我们的飞船坠落在地球时我才五岁
I was five when our ship crashed on earth.
我们离开母星时
When we left our home planet,
我父亲告诉我  我们正要经历冒险...
my father told me we were going on the adventure...
我是红鹰的长老
I am the grand patriarch of the Red Hawks.
长久以来
For too long,
政府都在隐瞒奥特里安人的真相
the government has hidden the truth about Atrians
但在今天
but today,
我们想让你们看到他们不可告人的一面
we'll show you what they don't want you to see.
终有一天  我们会摧毁围墙
One day, we're gonna break down these walls,
到时你们会后悔的
and you'll be sorry.
把视频关掉
Get that video down!
外星魔鬼
Alien demons,
他们不想和我们打成一片
they don't want to assimilate with us.
他们想歼灭我们
They want to annihilate us.
我们向天发誓
And hand to god,
我们会把他们所有人都送去地狱
we will send every last one of them back to hell!
禁区
不得跨越
我们要怎么做
What are we gonna do?
我名叫罗曼
My name is Roman.
我是诺克斯的儿子
I'm the son of Nox,
他是奥特里安人的已故首领
the late leader of the Atrians.
我上台是要说  你们刚见到的
I'm here to say that what you just saw...
有些内容属实
There is some truth to that.
注意
奥特里安飞船技术仍可操作
我们没有互帮互助  彼此学习
Instead of helping or learning from each other,
反而不遗余力隐瞒真相
we go to great lengths to hide the truth.
视频本该是奥特里安人讲述登陆日故事
Video was supposed be of Atrians telling their Arrival Day stories.
我想分享我的故事
I'd like to share mine.
那个红鹰说人类不想我们来地球
That Red Hawk said that humans don't want us here.
我知道这与事实相悖
Well, I know that's not true.
因为登陆那天
Because on arrival day,
我遇到一个人类女孩  她救了我的命
I met a human girl who saved my life.
要不是因为她  我今天也不会出现在这里
I wouldn't be here today if it wasn't for her.
可如果我今天遇到她
But if I met her today,
我们不可能一起沿街散步
we couldn't walk down the street together
却不对我们中至少一人造成伤害
without causing harm to one or both of us.
这就是我们所处世界的现实
That's the reality of our world.
融合项目并不完美
The integration program isn't perfect.
可它已经告诉了我
But it has shown me
像那个女孩一样的人类
that there are more humans out there like that girl
比红鹰更多
than there are Red Hawks.
这就给了我希望
And that gives me hope,
希望有一天
hope that someday,
我们能团结在一起
we will be able to come together.
求你别这样  求你了
Please don't do it. Please?
求你别杀了我  求你了  求你了
Please don't kill me, please, please?
我有家庭
I have a family.
他醒来时就都不记得了
He won't remember a thing when he wakes up.
你怎么知道
How'd you know?
我妈是龙头帮的首领
My mother is a leader of the Trags.
我不知道的可不多
There's not much I don't know.
可你为什么现在来帮忙
But why are you helping out now?
是时候接受我的命运了
It's time I embraced my destiny.
干得好
Nicely done.
要不是你的发言
If it wasn't for your speech,
融合项目和你父亲的努力
the integration program and your father's work
就都前功尽弃了
would've gone down the drain.
但你不会放弃融合的
You wouldn't have given up on integration, though.
对
No.
但我只对管用的项目感兴趣
But I'm only interested in programs that work.
多亏了你  这个项目还有用
Thanks to you, this one still does.
罗曼  你有什么评价吗
Roman, do you have a comment?
正如你们所见
As you saw,
罗曼代表着他这一代的
Roman represents the candor
率直和乐观
and optimism of his generation,
这为这整个国家和世界的融合团结
which will pave the way for integration across this nation
铺平了道路
and the world.
去找格雷森  告诉他我们准备走了
Find Grayson, tell him we're ready to leave.
真不敢相信我们耐着性子听完
I can't believe we had sit through Gloria
格洛丽亚讲完融合计划
prattle on about integration.
看到我们的视频放出来时她的表情
It was worth it to see the look on her face
也算是值了
when our video came on.
你确定他们没法追踪到我们和格雷森吗
And you're sure they can't trace it back to us or Grayson?
我处理好了  别担心了
I handled it. Stop worrying.
-埃默里  -别碰我
- Emery. - Don't touch me!
埃默里  听我解释
Emery, let me explain.
Emery, let me explain!
解释什么
Explain what?
你父亲不是红鹰的长老
Your father isn't the grand patriarch for the Red Hawks,
他没有用我们拍的录像
that he didn't use the footage we shot
合成那个可怕的视频吗
for that horrible video?!
我不能这样说
I can't tell you that.
我的天
Oh, my god...
你利用我去隔离区拍录像
You used me so you could shoot in the Sector.
不  我父母是红鹰  好吧
No! My parents are who they are, okay,
可我不是
but I am not a Red Hawk.
我不相信你
I don't believe you.
是真的  他们一定是昨晚
It's true. They must have stolen the video
偷了我的视频
from me last night.
你父亲说了那些话
The things your father said,
你们怎么还能在同一屋檐下生活
how could you live under the same roof?
埃默里  我理解你的感受
Emery, I understand how you feel.
我每天都承受着这些
I live with it every day.
我只是假装和红鹰相处融洽
I just pretend to get along with the Red Hawks.
可...
But...
他们是我的父母
They're my parents.
我没法和你相处
I can't be around you right now.
罗曼
Roman.
之前和你在一起的警卫  博蒙特
That guard I saw you with earlier-- Beaumont.
他要干什么
What'd he want?
-没事  -有事
- It was nothing. - It wasn't nothing.
他是龙头帮的  是个危险人物
He's a Trag and he's dangerous.
我们不用向你做解释
We don't have to explain ourselves to you.
你也没必要假装关心我们了
And you don't have to pretend to care about us anymore.
罗曼
Roman!
成功了
It worked!
It worked.
谢谢
Thank you.
你给我带来了我要的
You brought me what I asked for.
更重要的是
More importantly,
你让我女儿浪子回头了
you brought my daughter to the fold.
我不做自我斗争了
I'm not conflicted anymore.
我知道我的信仰所在
I know where my loyalties lie.
你现在是龙头帮的同胞兄弟
You are now a full brother of the Trags.
我们将消灭你的敌人
We will spill the blood of your enemies
正如你已消灭我们的敌人
as you have spilled the blood of ours.
作为你完成任务的奖励
As a reward for completing your mission...
你将看到即将到来的事
You'll have a glimpse of what is to come.
这是柏草
That's cyper.
和你之前看到的不同
Not as you've seen it before.
我们将把黑柏草用到人类身上
we will unleash black cyper on the humans.
有你这样的忠实士兵
With loyal soldiers like yourself,
他是个叛徒
He was a traitor.
我们的一个间谍
One of our spies
看到他背着我们把情报给卡斯特
caught him giving information to Castor behind our back.
允许进入
我的儿子
Oh, here's my boy.
妈妈
Mommy!